#### Jacob May

#### Huddersfield, HD4 7HL

Phone: 07780685832

Email: Jacob-may@outlook.com

Dynamic and adaptable professional with a background in outdoor adventure training, sales, and collaborative team environments.

Learning to code has been an enriching experience, constantly inspiring new projects and unique ideas. I'm committed to continuous self-improvement and excited to channel creativity and dedication into upcoming coding projects.

Demonstrated proficiency in a wide array of technologies including:

Frontend Development: HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, Typescript

• Frameworks & Libraries: Next.js, React, Angular

• Backend Development: Express/Node.js

• Databases: MongoDB/Mongoose

Testing: Jest, Postman, Thunder Client

• Deployment: Render, Vercel, Google Analytics

• Version Control: Git and GitHub

#### **Work History**

Sales Executive/Representative Advanced Technical Panels, James Latham May 2019 – November 2023,

Royal Marine Commando Recruit Training May 2017 - May 2019,

Lifeguard and Labourer Vertex Ropes Access October 2016 – December 2016,

Watersports Instructor (Windsurf/Sailing) Ocean Elements August 2016 - October 2016,

Watersports Instructor (Windsurf/Sailing) Neilson, Greece January 2016 – August 2016,

Activity Instructor/Group Leader Kingswood/PGL September 2014 – November 2015,

Window Cleaner February 2013 - September 2013; July 2014 - September 2014,

Tesco Customer Assistant April 2012 – February 2013,

## **Education**

## AS level:

- A ICT
- B English Language
- D Biology

## GCSE:

- B's Mathematics, English Literature, Science, Information technology
- C's Religious education, Additional Science, English Language, Statistics

# **Hobbies and Interests**

Coding and Web Development, Exploring New Technologies, Pets, Socialising, Outdoor Adventure Activities.